<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>BigNtertainment</title>
    <link>https://bigntertainment.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BigNtertainment</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://bigntertainment.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://bigntertainment.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:41:39 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bigntertainment.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release of Crackhead Adventures v1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://bigntertainment.github.io/post/crackhead-adventures-1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:41:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bigntertainment.github.io/post/crackhead-adventures-1.1/</guid>
      <description>First Update for Crackhead Adventures is here! Bringing new features and bugfixes.
Things we added: Stats screen after completing the game that tracks: enemies killed damage taken shots fired cocaine snorted cocaine collected fun dust snorted fun dust crafted Settings menu that lets you change volume of music and sfx Version label in the main menu Things we fixed: A bug where the player couldn&amp;rsquo;t get hit when near an enemy A Bug where the player could shoot through walls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release of Crackhead Adventures v1.0.0</title>
      <link>https://bigntertainment.github.io/post/crackhead-adventures-1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 21:49:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bigntertainment.github.io/post/crackhead-adventures-1.0/</guid>
      <description>Today we released Crackhead Adventures version 1.0.0! We had great fun developing the game so far. We plan on improving on the current state of the project and listening to the feedback of our community.
So, what changed? We added a timer for players to compare their speed We fixed a major bug that allowed the player to walk into walls Our plans for now Adding a setting menu with volume sliders Adding additional stats at the end of the playthrough Changing the effect of the fun dust Fixing bugs Begin working on the new game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started working on the website</title>
      <link>https://bigntertainment.github.io/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:36:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bigntertainment.github.io/post/first/</guid>
      <description>We are now working on the official BigNtertainment website. It should be up and running by the half of September. After that we&amp;rsquo;re going to add our own theme to make the website stand out more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crackhead Adventures</title>
      <link>https://bigntertainment.github.io/project/crackhead-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bigntertainment.github.io/project/crackhead-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Crackhead Adventures: Give me your fun dust or I will f*cking murder you (WGJ Edition) by BigNtertainment CONTENT WARNING! The game contains mature content, such as narcotics.
TRIGGER WARNING! The game contains flashing images that might trigger epileptic seizures.
Controls:
WASD - movement Mouse - aiming and shooting E - snort cocaine (be faster, heal a bit) R - take the f u n d u s t (be a hella faster, but leaves you with almost no health) T - craft f u n d u s t from 3 bags of cocaine You are a drug-hungry crackhead fighting against the mafia to obtain the ultimate drug - the f u n n i e s t d u s t.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
